export const alphabetQuestions = [
  { questionText: "ا", correctAnswer: "A" },
  { questionText: "ب", correctAnswer: "B" },
  { questionText: "پ", correctAnswer: "P" },
  { questionText: "ت", correctAnswer: "T" },
  { questionText: "ج", correctAnswer: "J" },
  { questionText: "چ", correctAnswer: "Ch" },
  { questionText: "خ", correctAnswer: "X" },
  { questionText: "د", correctAnswer: "D" },
  { questionText: "ر", correctAnswer: "R" },
  { questionText: "ز", correctAnswer: "Z" },
  { questionText: "ژ", correctAnswer: "Zh" },
  { questionText: "س", correctAnswer: "S" },
  { questionText: "ش", correctAnswer: "Sh" },
  { questionText: "غ", correctAnswer: "Gh" },
  { questionText: "ف", correctAnswer: "F" },
  { questionText: "ق", correctAnswer: "Q" },
  { questionText: "ك", correctAnswer: "K" },
  { questionText: "گ", correctAnswer: "G" },
  { questionText: "ڭ", correctAnswer: "Ng" },
  { questionText: "ل", correctAnswer: "L" },
  { questionText: "م", correctAnswer: "M" },
  { questionText: "ن", correctAnswer: "N" },
  { questionText: "ھ", correctAnswer: "H" },
  { questionText: "و", correctAnswer: "O / U" },
  { questionText: "ئۇ", correctAnswer: "U" },
  { questionText: "ئۆ", correctAnswer: "O" },
  { questionText: "ۈ", correctAnswer: "Ü" },
  { questionText: "ۋ", correctAnswer: "V" },
  { questionText: "ي", correctAnswer: "Y / I" },
  { questionText: "ې", correctAnswer: "E" },
];
